Guide to the Yale Dramatic Association Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Show Files, Series II
  - 1066 - And All That, 1938 Feb, Nov, December (Box 22, Folder 21-22)
  - Thieves' Carnival, 1961 Feb, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 23-24)
  - This Woman Business, 1928 February (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Three Penny Opera, 1966 Apr, June (Box 22, Folder 26-27)
  - Timon of Athens, 1940 January (Box 22, Folder 28-30)
  - Tom Jones, 1960 April, April-June (Box 22, Folder 31-34)
  - Tom Thumb the Great, 1941 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Too Many Boys, 1940 March 9, 11, 12, April 27 (Box 23, Folder 2-3)
  - Too Much Johnson, 1942 February 27-28, March 7 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Too True to be Good, 1953 November 19-21 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Too True to be Good, 1953 November (Box 23, Folder 6-7)
  - Train Time, 1942 April 24-25 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Troilus and Cressida, 1916 June 17 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - The Truth about Blayds, 1930 February 4, 12 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Twelfth Night, 1968 April (Box 23, Folder 11-13)
  - The Two Gentlemen of Verona, 1934 June (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - A View from the Bridge, 1957 March (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Waiting for Godot, 1960 Feb, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 16-17)
  - Waiting for Godot, 1967 February (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - The War of the Worlds, 1956 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Waterbury Tales, 1941 March 1, 3, 4, 7 December (Box 23, Folder 20-21)
  - The Weavers, 1937 February 22, March 2 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - What Makes Sammy Run? (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - What the Butler Saw, 1971 May (Box 23, Folder 24-26)
  - When in Rome, 1942 June (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Whispering Gallery, 1935 November 30 December 2, 4 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - White Wings, 1928 December 1929 February 2, 5 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Wings Over Europe, 1936 March 3, 4, 7 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Winterset, 1938 March 9, 1948 November 11-13 (Box 23, Folder 31-32)
  - The Yale Animal, 1953 April 30 May 2 June 5, 6 (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Yellowjack, 1935 March (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - You Can't Take It With You, 1950 April 27-29 (Box 23, Folder 35-36)
  - Freshman One Acts, 1947 October 17-18, 1957 January 12-14, 1957 December, 1959 December, 1960-1961 December (Box 23, Folder 37-45)
  - Freshman One Acts, 1963 December 19, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 46-47)
  - Freshman One Acts, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 48)
  - Freshman One Acts, empty Folder/discarded, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 49)
  - Ben Greet's Company, 1903 May 25 (Box 23, Folder 50)
  - Ben Greet's Woodland Players, 1904 June 1 (Box 23, Folder 51)
  - Maude Adams Benefit: Twelfth Night, 1908 June 5 (Box 23, Folder 52)
  - Maude Adams Benefit: What Every Woman Knows, 1909 April 19 (Box 23, Folder 53)
  - Iphigenia in Tauris, 1915 May 15 (Box 23, Folder 54-55)
  - John Masefield Lecture, 1916 March 10 (Box 23, Folder 56)
  - Sir Arthur Conan Doyle on Spiritualism, 1922 (Box 23, Folder 57)
  - Tony Sarg Marionettes: Rip Van Winkle, 1922 April 26 (Box 23, Folder 58)
  - Tony Sarg Marionettes: Don Quixote, 1922 December 6 (Box 23, Folder 59)
  - Raquel Meller Recital, 1926 November 16 (Box 23, Folder 60)
  - Tony Sarg Marionettes: The Arabian Nights, 1926 November 30 (Box 23, Folder 61)
  - John Masefield Lecture, 1933 January 16 (Box 23, Folder 62)
  - Sir John Gielgud: The Ages of Man, 1960 December 8 (Box 23, Folder 63)
  - National Theatre of the Deaf, 1972 October 18 (Box 23, Folder 64)
  - New York Mime Duet, 1975 December 6 (Box 23, Folder 65)
  - Antigone (proposed production), 1976 (Box 35)
  - Anyone can Whistle, 1976 February - March (Box 35)
  - The Effect of Gamma Rays on Man-in-the Moon Marigolds, 1976 March (Box 35)
  - Gypsy, 1978 Spring (Box 35)
  - Hot L Baltimore, 1976 March (Box 35)
  - Let's Do It, 1976 May (Box 35)
  - Let's Do It (encore), 1976 November (Box 35)
  - Makin' Light, 1979 June (Box 35)
  - Freshmen One Acts, 1976 February (Box 35)
- Programs of Yale Dramat, 1899 - 1981; Series III
  - The Pardoner's Tale and The Second Shepherds' Play (2 copies), 1900 May 23 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - The Fair Maid of the West (2 copies), 1900-1901 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Bicentennial Celebration, 1901 October 22 (Box 24, Folder 3, Item 1)
  - The Critic and High Life Below Stairs (2 copies), 1902 April (Box 24, Folder 3, Item 2)
  - The Good Natured Man (2 copies), 1903 April (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - New Men and Old Acres, 1904 April (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - NO PROGRAM (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - King Henry IV Part One, 1906 April 3 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - The Amazons (2 copies), 1907 January (Box 24, Folder 8, Item 1)
  - The Pretenders (2 copies), 1907 April (Box 24, Folder 8, Item 2)
  - El Doctor y El Infermo, Einer Muss Hiralen and Le Pretexte, 1907 November (Box 24, Folder 9, Item 1)
  - Revizor (2 copies), 1908 April (Box 24, Folder 9, Item 3)
  - The Critic and The Fire Eater, 1908 December (Box 24, Folder 10, Item 1)
  - The Merry Wives of Windsor, 1909 January (Box 24, Folder 10, Item 3)
  - London Assurance, [acting version included] (2 copies), 1909 December (Box 24, Folder 11, Item 1)
  - The Taming of the Shrew (2 copies), 1910 January (Box 24, Folder 11, Item 2)
  - Il Ventaglio, 1910 December-1911 January (Box 24, Folder 12, Item 1)
  - The Knight of the Burning Pestle, 1911 June (Box 24, Folder 12, Item 2)
  - The Devil's Disciple (2 copies), 1911 December-1912 January (Box 24, Folder 13, Item 1)
  - And the Villain Still Pursues Her (2 copies), 1912 April (Box 24, Folder 13, Item 2)
  - Robin of Sherwood, 1912 June
    See: Crawford Theater collection (MS 1387)
  - Fruits of Culture, 1912 December-1913 January (Box 24, Folder 14, Item 1)
  - The Kaleidoscope, 1913 April (Box 24, Folder 14, Item 2)
  - The Recruiting Officer (2 copies), 1913 June (Box 24, Folder 14, Item 3)
  - Shades of Night, Fritzchen and Gringoire, 1913 December-1914 January (Box 24, Folder 15, Item 1)
  - Quentin Durward (2 copies), 1914 June (Box 24, Folder 15, Item 5)
  - Beyond the Beyond, The Ghost of Jerry Bundler, St. Bartholomew's Eve, and The Stranger (2 copies), 1915 February (Box 24, Folder 16, Item 1)
  - Harold, 1915 June (Box 24, Folder 16, Item 5)
  - An Ideal Husband (3 copies), 1916 March (Box 24, Folder 17, Item 1)
  - Her Husband's Wife (2 copies), 1916 April (Box 24, Folder 17, Item 2)
  - Troilus and Cressida (4 copies), 1916 June (Box 24, Folder 17, Item 3)
  - Ours, 1916 December-1917 February (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - The Message and Jehanne, Tancred, The Second Mrs. Otcott, and The Aulis Difficulty, 1917 December 20 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - The Aulis Difficulty, Nettie, The Murderers, and Bunk, 1919 February-March (Box 24A, Folder 1, Item 1)
  - Nerves, Autonomy, Good Old Medusa (2 copies), 1919 April (Box 24A, Folder 1, Item 5)
  - Tamburlaine, 1919 June (Box 24A, Folder 1, Item 8)
  - The Lodger, 1920 February-March (Box 24A, Folder 2, Item 1)
  - Curfew, Night Life, The Road, The Complaint of the King of the Golden Isles, 1920 April (Box 24A, Folder 2, Item 2)
  - Henry IV, Part I, 1920 June (Box 24A, Folder 2, Item 6)
  - A Successful Calamity, 1921 February-March (Box 24A, Folder 3, Item 1)
  - The Robber, Revelation, The Robbery, A Night at the Inn, 1921 April (Box 24A, Folder 3, Item 2)
  - Fall Entertainment, 1921-1922 (Box 24A, Folder 4, Item 1)
  - Caesar and Cleopatra, 1922 January (Box 24A, Folder 4, Item 2)
  - The Rhesus of Euripides (2 copies), 1922 June (Box 24A, Folder 4, Item 3)
  - The Playboy of the Western World, 1923 February, April (Box 24A, Folder 5, Item 1)
  - King Lear (5 copies), 1923 June (Box 24A, Folder 5, Item 2)
  - The Faun (2 copies), 1924 February-April (Box 24A, Folder 6, Item 1)
  - The Frogs, 1924 June (Box 24A, Folder 6, Item 2)
  - The Frogs, 1924 October (Box 24A, Folder 7, Item 1)
  - The Galloper (3 copies), 1924 December-1925 May (Box 24A, Folder 7, Item 2)
  - L'Aiglon (2 copies), 1925 June (Box 24A, Folder 7, Item 3)
  - L'Aiglon, 1925 October (Box 24A, Folder 8, Item 1)
  - Out O'Luck (2 copies), 1925 December-1926 April (Box 24A, Folder 8, Item 2)
  - Drama of Orestes, 1926 June (Box 24A, Folder 8, Item 3)
  - Bold Bad Men (3 copies), 1927 February, April (Box 24A, Folder 9, Item 2)
  - Coriolanus, 1927 June (Box 24A, Folder 9, Item 3)
  - This Woman Business (2 copies), 1927 December-1928 February (Box 24A, Folder 10, Item 1)
  - Macbeth (3 copies), 1928 June (Box 24A, Folder 10, Item 2)
  - White Wings, 1929 February (Box 24A, Folder 11, Item 1)
  - Reunion, 1929 May (Box 24A, Folder 11, Item 2)
  - Saint Carlo Saves the Day, The March of El-Ratan, Captain Brassbound's Conversation, 1929 May-June (Box 24A, Folder 11, Item 3)
  - Captain Brassbound's Conversion, 1929 November-1930 January (Box 24A, Folder 12, Item 1)
  - The Truth About Blayds, 1930 February (Box 24A, Folder 12, Item 2)
  - Trafalgar Square, The Locked Door, Pity, The Banana Murder Case, 1930 May (Box 24A, Folder 12, Item 3)
  - The Roof, 1930 June (Box 24A, Folder 13, Item 1)
  - The Racket, 1930 November (Box 24A, Folder 13, Item 2)
  - Outward Bound, 1931 February (Box 24A, Folder 13, Item 3)
  - The Miser, 1931 May (Box 24A, Folder 13, Item 4)
  - The Miser, 1931 June (Box 24A, Folder 13, Item 5)
  - The Long Christmas Dinner, Such Things Only Happen in Books, The Happy Journey to Trenton and Camden, Love and How to Cure It, 1931 November (Box 24A, Folder 14, Item 1)
  - Julius Caesar (5 copies), 1932 March (Box 24A, Folder 14, Item 5)
  - The Perfect Alibi [includes sheet music], 1932 June (Box 24A, Folder 14, Item 6)
  - The Perfect Alibi, 1932 October, December (Box 24A, Folder 15, Item 1)
  - The Private Secretary (2 copies), 1932 November (Box 24A, Folder 15, Item 2)
  - Brown of Harvard, Circa 1933 (Box 24A, Folder 15, Item 3)
  - Much Ado About Nothing, 1933 May (Box 24A, Folder 15, Item 4)
  - Much Ado About Nothing, 1933 October (Box 24A, Folder 16, Item 1)
  - The Swan (2 copies), 1933 November-December (Box 24A, Folder 16, Item 2)
  - In the Days of the Turbins, 1934 March (Box 24A, Folder 16, Item 3)
  - Two Gentlemen of Verona (2 copies), 1934 June (Box 24A, Folder 16, Item 4)
  - Around the World in Eighty Days (3 copies), 1934 November-December (Box 24A, Folder 17, Item 1)
  - Yellow Jack (2 copies), 1935 March (Box 24A, Folder 17, Item 2)
  - Leave it to Psmith, 1935 April (Box 24A, Folder 17, Item 3)
  - Hippolytus, 1935 June (Box 24A, Folder 17, Item 4)
  - Chekhov farces, 1935 (Box 24A, Folder 18, Item 1)
  - The Whispering Gallery (2 copies), 1935 November (Box 24A, Folder 18, Item 2)
  - Wings Over Europe, 1936 March (Box 24A, Folder 18, Item 3)
  - The Servant of Two Masters, 1936 June (Box 24A, Folder 18, Item 4)
  - Weatherwise, The Long Voyage Home, The Happy Journey to Trenton and Camden, 1936 June (Box 24A, Folder 18, Item 5)
  - The Weavers, 1937 February-March (Box 24A, Folder 19, Item 2)
  - And for Yale, 1937 June (Box 24A, Folder 19, Item 1)
  - Stoke-hole, Not for the Gander, 100,000 Dollars, 1937 June (Box 24A, Folder 19, Item 4)
  - The Front Page, 1937 November (Box 24A, Folder 20, Item 1)
  - And for Yale (3 copies), 1937 December (Box 24A, Folder 20, Item 2)
  - 1066 and All That, 1938 March (Box 24A, Folder 20, Item 3)
  - Winterset (3 copies), 1938 March (Box 24A, Folder 20, Item 4)
  - The Comedy of Errors (2 copies), 1938 June (Box 24A, Folder 20, Item 5)
  - 1066 and All That (2 copies), 1938 December (Box 24A, Folder 21, Item 1-2)
  - Where the Cross Is Made, The Moving Finger, Waiting for Lefty, 1938 December (Box 24A, Folder 21, Item 3)
  - Here We Go Again (2 copies), 1939 January-April (Box 24A, Folder 21, Item 6)
  - The Play's The Thing, 1939 March (Box 24A, Folder 21, Item 7)
  - Fiesco (2 copies), 1939 June (Box 24A, Folder 21, Item 8)
  - Bury the Dead, Meet you at Room (2 copies), 1939-1940 (Box 24A, Folder 22, Item 1)
  - Rope's End, 1939 November (Box 24A, Folder 22, Item 3)
  - Timon of Athens (2 copies), 1940 January (Box 24A, Folder 22, Item 4)
  - Too Many Boys (2 copies), 1940 February-March (Box 24A, Folder 22, Item 5)
  - Hay Fever, 1940 March (Box 24A, Folder 22, Item 6)
  - The Jew of Malta, 1940 June (Box 24A, Folder 22, Item 7)
  - The Massacre at Paris (3 copies), 1940 October (Box 24A, Folder 23, Item 1)
  - Merton of the Movies (2 copies), 1940 November (Box 24A, Folder 23, Item 2)
  - The Hairy Ape (3 copies), 1941 January (Box 24A, Folder 23, Item 3)
  - Waterbury Tales (2 copies), 1941 February-March (Box 24A, Folder 23, Item 4)
  - Antony and Cleopatra, 1941 June (Box 24A, Folder 23, Item 5)
  - Here Comes the Clowns, 1941 April (Box 24A, Folder 23, Item 6)
  - Tom Thumb, 1941 October (Box 24A, Folder 24, Item 1)
  - The Frogs of Aristophanes, 1941 November (Box 24A, Folder 24, Item 2)
  - Waterbury Tales (2 copies), 1941 December (Box 24A, Folder 24, Item 3)
  - The Importance of Being Earnest, 1942 January (Box 24A, Folder 24, Item 4)
  - Too Much Johnson, 1942 February-March (Box 24A, Folder 24, Item 5)
  - Train Time, 1942 April (Box 24A, Folder 24, Item 6)
  - The Beautiful People (2 copies), 1942 May (Box 24A, Folder 24, Item 7)
  - When In Rome, 1942 June (Box 24A, Folder 24, Item 8)
  - The Petrified Forest, 1942 August (Box 24A, Folder 25, Item 1)
  - The Spider, 1942 September (Box 24A, Folder 25, Item 2)
  - Hayfoot, Strawfoot, 1942 October (Box 24A, Folder 25, Item 3)
  - Henry IV, Part I, 1943 April (Box 24A, Folder 25, Item 4)
    Was one of the two years of World War II during which the Dramat shut down, 1943-1944.
  - And for Yale, 1945-1946 (Box 24A, Folder 26, Item 1)
  - Beggar on Horseback, 1946 March (Box 24A, Folder 26, Item 2)
  - The Golden Boy, 1946 June (Box 24A, Folder 26, Item 3)
  - The Assassin (3 copies), 1946 October 18-19 (Box 24A, Folder 27, Item 1)
  - Knickerbocker Holiday, 1946 November (Box 24A, Folder 27, Item 2)
  - Fashion, 1947 March (Box 24A, Folder 27, Item 3)
  - Caligula, 1947 June (Box 24A, Folder 27, Item 5)
  - The Jubjub, Godiva's Morning After, Satan Takes the Count, 1947 October (Box 24A, Folder 28, Item 1)
  - In the Clover (2 copies), 1947 November (Box 24A, Folder 28, Item 4)
  - Room Service, 1948 February (Box 24A, Folder 28, Item 5)
  - Grand Guignol, 1948 April-May (Box 24A, Folder 28, Item 6)
  - The Fireman's Flame, 1948 June (Box 24A, Folder 28, Item 7)
  - Winterset, 1948 November (Box 24A, Folder 29, Item 1)
  - The Great Catherine, Free Speech (2 copies), 1949 January (Box 24A, Folder 29, Item 2)
  - Mind the Music, 1949 March (Box 24A, Folder 29, Item 4)
  - Mannerhouse, 1949 May (Box 24A, Folder 29, Item 5)
  - The Male Animal, 1949 June (Box 24A, Folder 29, Item 6)
  - All My Sons, 1949 October (Box 24A, Folder 30, Item 1)
  - Heads You Lose, 1949 November (Box 24A, Folder 30, Item 2)
  - Richard II (2 copies), 1950 March (Box 24A, Folder 30, Item 3)
  - You Can't Take It With You, 1950 April (Box 24A, Folder 30, Item 5)
  - The Play's the Thing, 1950 June (Box 24A, Folder 30, Item 6)
  - Harvey (2 copies), 1950 December (Box 24A, Folder 31, Item 1)
  - Kiss the Boys Good-bye, 1951 March (Box 24A, Folder 31, Item 2)
  - The Hasty Heart (2 copies), 1951 March (Box 24A, Folder 31, Item 3)
  - The Skin of Our Teeth (2 copies), 1951 May (Box 24A, Folder 31, Item 4)
  - The Man Who Came to Dinner, 1951 November (Box 24A, Folder 32, Item 1)
  - Amphitryon 38, 1952 February-March (Box 24A, Folder 32, Item 2)
  - The Birds (2 copies), 1952 May-June (Box 24A, Folder 32, Item 3)
  - The Much Muted Horn, The Wedding Night, The Greatest Man in the World, 1951-1952 (Box 24A, Folder 32, Item 4)
  - Six Characters in Search of An Author, 1952 November (Box 24A, Folder 33, Item 1)
  - The Great Adventure, The Dirty Old Beard, The Incurables (2 copies), 1952 December (Box 24A, Folder 33, Item 2)
  - Colombe, 1953 February-March (Box 24A, Folder 33, Item 3)
  - The Yale Animal (2 copies), 1953 April-May, June (Box 24A, Folder 33, Item 4)
  - Too True to be Good, 1953 November (Box 24A, Folder 34, Item 1)
  - The Tempest, 1954 February, May (Box 24A, Folder 34, Item 2)
  - Stover at Yale (3 copies), 1954 April-June (Box 24A, Folder 34, Item 3)
  - Stover at Yale, 1954 October (Box 24A, Folder 35, Item 1)
  - The Downstairs Dragon, 1954 November (Box 24A, Folder 35, Item 2)
  - Lee, The Little Boy, The Great She-Bear, 1954 December (Box 24A, Folder 35, Item 3)
  - Tartuffe (2 copies), 1955 February-March (Box 24A, Folder 35, Item 4)
  - So What!, 1955 April, June (Box 24A, Folder 35, Item 5)
  - A Miracle of St. Anthony, Gamblers, The Happy Journey, 1955-1956 (Box 24A, Folder 36, Item 1)
  - All the Way Home, The Rebels, Come to the Party, 1955 December (Box 24A, Folder 36, Item 4)
  - The Scarecrow, 1956 winter (Box 24A, Folder 36, Item 5)
  - The Great Gatsby, 1956 June (Box 24A, Folder 36, Item 6)
  - The Lady's Not for Burning, 1956 November (Box 24A, Folder 37, Item 1)
  - Facade, The Emperor of Biloxi, The Barge She Sat On (3 copies), 1957 January (Box 24A, Folder 37, Item 2)
  - A View from the Bridge, 1957 March (Box 24A, Folder 37, Item 5)
  - La Ronde, 1957 May-June (Box 24A, Folder 37, Item 6)
  - The Crucible, 1957 November (Box 24A, Folder 38, Item 1)
  - That Impossible Trip to the Moon, Hang Dog, Night Song, Stranger in These Parts, 1957 December (Box 24A, Folder 38, Item 2-5)
  - The Skin of Our Teeth, 1958 February-March (Box 24A, Folder 38, Item 6)
  - Cyrano (4 copies), 1958 April-May (Box 24A, Folder 39, Item 1)
  - Danton's Death, 1958 November (Box 24A, Folder 39, Item 2)
  - Sea of Tweed, Under the Cheesecake, Mine Eye Poureth Out Tears, 1958 December (Box 24A, Folder 39, Item 3)
  - The Inspector General, 1959 February-March (Box 24A, Folder 39, Item 4)
  - Grand Tour, 1959 April-May (Box 24A, Folder 39, Item 5)
  - Julius Caesar, 1959 November (Box 24A, Folder 40, Volume 1)
  - Honor, The Open Window, Emerald in the Sunlight, 1959 December (Box 24A, Folder 40, Item 2)
  - Waiting for Godot (2 copies), 1960 February (Box 24A, Folder 40, Item 3)
  - A Sleep of Prisoners (3 copies), 1959 December (Box 24A, Folder 40, Item 4)
  - Tom Jones, 1960 April-June (Box 24A, Folder 40, Item 5)
    Photographic negatives included.
  - Camino Real, 1960 November (Box 24A, Folder 41, Item 1)
  - Open Your Mouths and Sing Blues, To Be Dead, The Wheel, 1960 December (Box 24A, Folder 41, Item 2)
  - Thieves' Carnival, 1961 February (Box 24A, Folder 41, Item 3)
  - Booth is Back in Town, 1961 May-June (Box 24A, Folder 41, Item 4)
  - Henry VI, Part III, 1961 November-December (Box 24A, Folder 42, Item 1)
  - Arsenic and Old Lace, 1962 February (Box 24A, Folder 42, Item 2)
  - Finian's Rainbow, 1962 April, June (Box 24A, Folder 42, Item 3)
  - Artist's Life, The Plays, The Second Instinct, Metaphase (2 copies), 1962 (Box 24A, Folder 42, Item 4)
  - Caucasian Chalk Circle, 1962 November (Box 24A, Folder 43, Item 1)
  - Playboy of the Western World, 1963 February (Box 24A, Folder 43, Item 2)
  - Once Upon A Mattress, 1963 April-June (Box 24A, Folder 43, Item 3)
  - Men Without Shadows, 1963 November
  - Ernst Toller, Vault of Dreams, The Death of Ivan Ilych (3 copies), 1963 December (Box 24A, Folder 44, Item 1)
  - Good Soldier Schweik (2 copies), 1964 February (Box 24A, Folder 44, Item 4)
  - Taming of the Shrew (2 copies), 1964 April, June (Box 24A, Folder 44, Item 5)
  - Breaking Point, 1965 February (Box 24A, Folder 45, Item 2)
  - The Country Wife, 1965 May-June (Box 24A, Folder 45, Item 3)
  - The Death of Doctor Faust, 1965 November (Box 24A, Folder 46, Item 1)
  - The Threepenny Opera, 1966 April, June (Box 24A, Folder 46)
    See also: Crawford Theater collection (MS 1387)
  - The Shoemaker's Holiday, 1966 November (Box 24A, Folder 47)
    See: Crawford Theater collection (MS 1387). This folder contains only the cross-reference sheet.
  - Waiting for Godot, 1967 February-March
  - Hunger and Thirst, 1967 April-June
  - Dark of the Moon, 1967 November (Box 24A, Folder 48, Item 1)
  - The Hostage, 1968 February-March
  - Twelfth Night, 1968 May (Box 24A, Folder 48, Item 2)
  - Rhinoceros, 1968 November (Box 24A, Folder 49, Item 1)
  - The Balcony, 1969 February (Box 24A, Folder 49, Item 2)
  - A Funny Thing Happened on the Way to the Forum, 1969 April-June (Box 24A, Folder 49, Item 3)
  - Serjeant Musgrave's Dance, 1969 November
  - Him, 1970 February-March
  - Romeo and Juliet (2 copies), 1970 May-June (Box 24A, Folder 50, Item 1)
  - Rosencrantz and Guildenstern Are Dead, 1970 November (Box 24A, Folder 51, Item 1)
  - Oh, What A Lovely War!, 1970 November-December
  - What the Butler Saw, 1971 April-June (Box 24A, Folder 51, Item 2)
  - Peer Gynt (2 copies), 1971 November-December (Box 24A, Folder 52, Item 1)
  - Enemies, 1972 February-March (Box 24A, Folder 52, Item 2)
  - Beyond the Fringe, 1972 April (Box 24A, Folder 52, Item 3)
  - Little Mary Sunshine (3 copies), 1973 February-March (Box 24A, Folder 53, Item 1)
  - Misalliance, 1973 April or May (Box 24A, Folder 53, Item 2)
  - Anything Goes, 1973 November-December (Box 24A, Folder 54, Item 1)
  - Paradise Hotel (2 copies), 1974 April-May (Box 24A, Folder 54, Item 2)
  - Pal Joey, 1974 November-December (Box 24A, Folder 55, Item 1)
  - The House of Blue Leaves, Little Murders, 1975 February-March (Box 24A, Folder 55, Item 2)
  - Pericles, 1975 April (Box 24A, Folder 55)
  - As You Like It (3 copies), 1975 March-April (Box 24A, Folder 55, Item 5)
  - Pantagleize, 1975 November (Box 35)
  - Anyone can Whistle (3 copies), 1976 February (Box 35)
  - The Poet and the Hag, Piglet, Freshman Blues, 1976 February (Box 35)
  - Hot L Baltimore, 1976 March (Box 35)
  - Let's Do It, 1976 May (Box 35)
  - When You Comin' Back, Red Ryder?, 1977 November (Box 24A, Folder 56, Item 3)
  - Gypsy, 1978 February (Box 24A, Folder 56, Item 1)
  - Ace of Clubs, 1978 May (Box 24A, Folder 56, Item 2)
  - Starting Here! Starting Now!, 1978 September (Box 24A, Folder 57, Item 1)
  - The Philanthropist, 1978 October (Box 24A, Folder 57, Item 2)
  - Cabaret, 1978 November (Box 24A, Folder 57, Item 3)
  - The Boys in the Band, 1979 February (Box 24A, Folder 57, Item 4)
  - The Miracle Worker, 1979 February (Box 24A, Folder 57, Item 5)
  - Makin' Light, 1979 May (Box 24A, Folder 57, Item 6)
  - for colored girls who have considered suicide when the rainbow if enuf, 1979 October (Box 24A, Folder 58, Item 1)
  - Who's Afraid of Virginia Woolf?, 1979 October (Box 24A, Folder 58, Item 2)
  - Anything Goes, 1979 November (Box 24A, Folder 58, Item 3)
  - Trouble in Tahiti, 1980 February (Box 24A, Folder 58, Item 4)
  - Ladies in Waiting, 1980 February (Box 24A, Folder 58, Item 7)
  - Scapino, 1980 April (Box 24A, Folder 58, Item 5)
  - Déjà Revue, 1980 May (Box 24A, Folder 58, Item 6)
  - The Princess and the Woodcutter, Circa 1980 (Box 24A, Folder 59, Item 1)
  - Angry Ingrid, Circa 1980 (Box 24A, Folder 59, Item 2)
  - The Glass Menagerie, 1980 October (Box 24A, Folder 59, Item 3)
  - Design for Living, 1980 October (Box 24A, Folder 59, Item 4)
  - Heartbreak House, 1981 February (Box 24A, Folder 59, Item 6)
  - Tentative Plans, 1981 February-March (Box 24A, Folder 59, Item 5)
  - Peter Pan, 1981 April (Box 24A, Folder 59, Item 7)
  - Turning Blue, 1981 May (Box 24A, Folder 59, Item 8)
  - Playcraftsmen Programs
    - The Pipe, or the Faun Who Turned Monk, Quack, It Was the Best Butler, 1925 May 12 (Box 24A, Folder 60, Item 1)
    - Illusion, Daniels in the Lion's Den, The Seriousness of Frivolity, 1925 November 24 (Box 24A, Folder 60, Item 4)
    - Right Cross, Loggerhead, Broken Music, Tin Pan Alley (2 copies), 1926 April 13 (Box 24A, Folder 60, Item 7)
    - Vawdavil, Hurricane in a Hat (2 copies), 1926 June 1, 4 (Box 24A, Folder 60, Item 11)
    - Rhapsody in Black, Union, Rigamarole, Illusion, 1927 May 5-6 (Box 24A, Folder 60, Item 13)
    - Tribunal, For a Man, Deadline, 1927 November 10-11 (Box 24A, Folder 60, Item 17)
    - Genius, The Biddie Sweeps Out, Pegasus Stumbles, 1928 May 17 (Box 24A, Folder 60, Item 20)